在左侧，我们可以看到...
在右边我们可以看到...
...头上的咆哮者
一切都安全。
万无一失。
情绪？
小心！
你受伤了吗？
我不这么认为。
您？
我可以。
起床。
情绪 这里不安全。
我们走吧。
下一步是什么？
你会看到的！
情绪
这条路。
跟着我！
敢快 Emo!
你没有集中注意力。
我刚刚只是想回答...
...电话.
Emo. 看.
我是说听。
你必须学会倾听。
这是不是游戏。
你. 我指我们.
我们很容易在这里死亡。
听。
听机器的声音。
听你的呼吸。
好。 你不厌倦吗？
累?!?
Emo 机器就像发条。
一动不动...
...然后被打碎。
但是不是吗？
纸浆。 情绪！
那是你要的吗。 纸浆？
Emo. 您的人生目标...
...pulp?
Emo. 闭上你的眼睛。
Why?
- Now!
Ok.
Good.
您在左侧看到了什么。 情绪？
Nothing.
- Really?
No. nothing at all.
在你的右边。
您在右侧看到了什么。 情绪？
一样的普罗格。 一模一样...
...nothing!
- Great.
Listen Proog! Do you hear that!
Can we go here?
There?
It isn't safe. Emo.
But...
- Trust me. it's not.
Maybe I could...
No.
NO!
Any further questions. Emo?
No.
Emo?
Emo. why...
Emo...
...why can't you see
the beauty of this place?
The way it works.
How perfect it is.
No. Proog. I don't see.
I don't see because there's nothing there.
And why should I trust my
life to something that isn't there?
Well can you tell me that?
Answer me!
Proog...
...you're a sick man!
Stay away from me!
No! Emo! It's a trap!
Hah. it's a trap.
At the left side you can see
the hanging gardens of Babylon!
How's that for a trap?
No. Emo.
At the right side you can see...
...well guess what...
...the colossus of Rhodes!
No!
The colossus of Rhodes
and it is here just for you Proog.
It is there...
I'm telling you.
Emo...
...it is.